[Love in Pavilion]
[Episode 18]
If Jia Lan hadn't met me,
she might not have
suffered so much in her life.
I failed to keep her safe.
So…
I don't care how many people will die.
I don't care if it'll cost me my life.
You people don't deserve to live anyway.
Jiuhuo.
The Golden Dawn.
You've repaired the Golden Dawn?
Whether it's for humans or demons,
life is full of surprises.
The Golden Dawn is in my hands now.
I had given up hope,
but unexpectedly,
fortune smiled on me.
I doubt you can stop me now.
Let's go get Yitan and Quzhuo.
After him.
You've arrived just in time.
Join me
in welcoming Jia Lan's return.
Break!
She is
the evil creature
we encountered beyond the Boundary:
the Black Fox.
Lord Jiuhuo,
thank you for everything you did.
Jia Lan.
United as one.
United as one?
I despise such human nonsense the most.
Quzhuo!
The vessel for my soul is here as well.
She's not a vessel.
She is Dongfang Huaizhu!
You speak as if you have any say in this.
Quzhuo.
Hongye.
You all leave!
My brother was a lunatic
obsessed with talismans.
He left me thousands of them.
Today,
I'll show you what they can do.
Quzhuo!
Whether the ending can be changed or not,
I, Li Quzhuo,
was together with all my brothers
from the Mask Group today.
They're coming back.
-Huaizhu.
-Hongye.
-Zui.
Hongye.
Huaizhu.
Zui, are you alright?
I'm fine.
How are you?
Hongye.
Huaizhu, are you okay?
Hongye, Hongye!
Hongye!
Hongye.
Huaizhu.
Father.
It's good that you're home.
With me here,
Young Master Wangquan will be fine.
He brought you home safe.
I didn't expect
someone so young to be so brave.
Good.
I'm relieved that Hongye is alright.
Zui.
This room has the best lighting.
You can stay here.
Young Master Yang will stay across from you.
You guys must have a lot to talk about.
I'll leave you to it.
Thank you.
This place looks great.
Guess it was worth
getting dragged around by that girl
to repair all the magical artifacts
in the Divine Fire Villa.
Li Quzhuo.
Stand up.
What for?
I...
Y-You… W-What…
What are you doing?
It's really wonderful to see you
as soon as I'm back.
From now on,
I won't bully you ever again.
I'll be a thousand times nicer to you.
Zui,
you've changed.
Come on.
Call me Fourth Brother.
Fourth Brother.
Fourth Brother!
Tell me, what do you want?
I will do everything possible
to get it for you.
I just want you to stay alive.
And you guys,
I want you to stay alive too.
Well…
Something really bad
happened 20 years in the future, right?
So,
20 years later,
in the war between humans and demons,
the Yiqi Alliance was destroyed,
and the Mask Group suffered heavy losses.
And I
was the one who lived the longest.
You only made it back alive
because I
sacrificed myself?
So I was still super dope when I was old!
Why the long faces? You're all back now.
It means the ending
can definitely be changed.
Don't look so gloomy.
Smile.
You're right.
Since we're all back,
there must still be a chance.
Right. There's something
I need to discuss with you.
This magical artifact—
making and activating it
requires an enormous amount of energy.
This golden lotus
is basically wrecked.
But if I carefully repair it,
there's a chance it could be restored.
It must be destroyed.
Is it possible for Jiuhuo
to make
an exact replica of this thing?
That's not possible.
This golden lotus may not look like much,
but every component inside
is a rare treasure.
Good.
So we must destroy this thing
to cut off any chance
for Jiuhuo and the Black Fox
to enter our world.
[Shennong's Herbal Classics]
If one of us must die,
that person won't be you.
She's not a vessel.
She is Dongfang Huaizhu!
Why would you
go that far to save me?
I've never thought about it.
Then what have you thought about?
That I must never lose you.
Senior.
Master sent me to tell you
that Young Master Wangquan is fine.
You don't need to worry.
I'll go check on him now.
Junior Huaizhu,
when did you
hook up with Young Master Wangquan?
As your senior, I didn't even notice.
My affairs are none of your concern.
You favor Wangquan Hongye so much.
Isn't it just because
he's the heir of the Wangquan family?
One day,
I, Jin Renfeng,
will crush him beneath my feet.
Yitan.
Are you still thinking about Mu Mie?
When the Black Fox breaks the Boundary,
eternal night befalls.
I wonder how things
will turn out for Mu Mie.
Mu Mie's personality is just like yours.
I believe he won't give up hope.
Besides, as long as we change the future,
he'll be safe for sure.
Of course, if you really miss him,
after Aunt Yang Yan gives birth to him,
we'll go see him together. How about that?
Mu Mie did mention
that when he was six years old,
a masked guy
taught him to awaken his Clairvoyance.
But Quzhuo said
that two years later,
we'd all be dead.
Then who is that masked guy who will teach Mu Mie
Clairvoyance?
Enough. Don't say we'll die again.
Zui,
you'll surely live a long life.
You too, Yitan.
You'll also live a long life.
Because
I'll never leave your side in this lifetime.
Alright.
Then…
If I were to marry someone else,
would you still be like this?
Would you still
stay by my side so devotedly?
I would.
Yitan, that's a good answer.
But it's not the one I wanted.
That golden lotus—
you really burned it with a fire talisman?
Yes.
Don't worry. I burned it to ashes.
Gosh. You...
You're too brutal!
That magical artifact cost a fortune!
You should've at least picked a good day
and given it a grand funeral!
You're right.
I'll keep that in mind next time.
I...
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Look at your pouty face.
Come on, tell me. Who upset you?
I'll teach them a lesson for you.
Is it someone from the Divine Fire Villa?
It's that Jin Renfeng
with slanted eyes, right?
No.
It has nothing to do
with the Divine Fire Villa.
Then who is it?
Yitan?
I knew it!
It must be
because of that arranged marriage.
It's bothering you a lot, right?
Don't worry.
I'll go talk some sense into him right away.
Today, I'll make that brat
write you a letter
to break off the engagement.
As soon as he's done writing,
I'll rush it to the Wangquan Manor.
By then, before you even arrive,
you'll already be free.
I'm the best, aren't I?
Don't worry, Zui.
Yitan definitely has feelings for you.
I swear.
Really?
What do you mean?
Are you blind or what?
Haven't you noticed?
Since Zui returned from Sky City,
the way she looks at Yitan has changed.
She's already...
a young woman who's fallen in love.
She...
Don't tell me
you've fallen for Yang Yitan!
You fool!
Can't you get a grip on yourself?
Don't tell me he doesn't like you back!
Why are you up?
Sit down.
You've been taking care of me all this time?
You're much better now. Good.
Thank you.
Take your medicine first.
What about the others?
They're all fine. Don't worry.
That's good.
What did you dream about?
Every year on your death anniversary,
[To Hongye
From Huaizhu]
she'd bring a letter
to your cenotaph.
There aren't many letters
because 10 years
after you went beyond the Boundary,
she passed away.
Wangquan Hongye,
you're destined to lose your loved one.
All struggles are futile.
I dreamed…
we were very happy together.
So happy that
you gritted your teeth
and furrowed your brows?
The wound hurts.
Miss, if Young Master Wangquan is awake,
Master wants him to come over.
Alright, I see.
Your father wants to see me?
I should go then.
You're going like this?
When you see my father,
don't be nervous. Relax.
I'm not nervous.
The last dish is here!
Eat up.
Father, try a drumstick.
Qinlan, go back to your room and rest.
I need to
have a few words with Young Master Wangquan.
He's not your son-in-law.
What do you have to say to him?
I'll just sit here
and pour wine for you.
Sitting stiffly like this
isn't comfortable.
Why don't we relax a little?
Alright.
I have diabetes.
I can't drink alcohol.
You can help yourself to the wine.
Okay.
To you, Mr. Dongfang.
In the south, we always
have vinegar with our cold dishes.
You just drank vinegar.
It's appetizing.
Can you cook?
A real man
stays away from the kitchen.
Is that so?
These are all dishes that Huaizhu loves.
I made them.
A true gentleman
is good at cooking.
So, Young Master, are you a real man
or a true gentleman?
Well,
that depends on you, Mr. Dongfang.
I can be either.
I've heard that you're decisive and ruthless,
an unyielding tough guy.
I don't like tough guys.
Your ambition is to rule the world,
and you're destined for greatness.
Because of this, you
can't make pastries
or cook fish soup.
You can't take good care of my Huaizhu.
I can learn.
You know what I mean.
Huaizhu doesn't like power struggles,
but you're at the center of that storm.
Mr. Dongfang, please give me some time.
I'll certainly take care of everything.
As long as Huaizhu is happy,
I don't mind plain meals
and a quiet life.
You know what?
A lot of suitors
have come to ask for her hand,
but none of them
have had the privilege
of pouring me a cup of wine.
Yes.
Mr. Dongfang.
I like that smile of yours.
Don't sit there
like the stone lion outside my gate.
Come on, relax.
Let's have a good drink together
as father and son.
Sure.
Thank you, Mr. Dongfang.
Come on.
Cheers.
Don't drink alone.
I…
F-From now on,
if anyone else comes to propose,
I'll tell them
Huaizhu is already spoken for.
That's so kind of you.
You're so kind, Mr. Dongfang.
S-Stop calling me Mr. Dongfang.
Call me Big Brother.
Big Brother.
I have everything here at home,
except for good wine.
Big Brother,
I have good wine.
I'll have someone bring it over.
Bring it over.
Bro.
Have you kept in mind
everything I told you?
You're looking down on me.
Are you looking down on me?
Let me prove it to you.
L-Let me…
Go ahead.
Let me…
Huaizhu likes to eat
steamed lamb,
steamed bear paw,
steamed deer tail,
roasted duck,
roasted chick,
roasted gosling,
braised meat, braised duck,
soy sauce chicken,
cured meat, and pork knuckle with pine nuts…
Who said I like all those things?
Who said that?
Big Brother, I think I'm drunk.
Is Huaizhu here?
I saw her too.
First, who allowed you to drink, Father?
Who allowed it?
Second, was wine not enough
that you had to drink vinegar too?
That was vinegar!
-What vinegar?
-Vinegar…
Who said the Divine Fire Villa doesn't have good wine?
Who said that?
I did.
Throw him out!
Out?
My bro and I haven't had enough yet.
Not enough.
Bring more wine.
We've got plenty of wine.
I'll have Huaizhu bring it for you!
Bring… Bring it.
Huaizhu,
go get some wine.
Go get it now.
Someone!
Miss Huaizhu.
Bring them another pot of vinegar.
Let them sober up properly.
Yes.
Come on, bro.
I can't drink anymore.
Take it, take it.
Here.
Bro, drink.
You're awake?
Huaizhu, yesterday…
My…
My throat…
Young Master Wangquan not only loves wine
but also vinegar, huh?
Vinegar?
You don't remember?
Then let me remind you.
Besides rattling off dish names all night,
you also said
my father's cooking was too bland.
You even became sworn brothers with him.
So now I should call you—
That's enough.
Drink this hangover soup and then go back.
You're not angry, are you?
Vinegar isn't expensive.
Why would I be angry?
Besides, you slept well last night.
Your inner energy has also stabilized.
Then…
Don't you have
important matters to attend to?
Take two of these pills a day.
They're enough for seven days.
After seven days…
I'll come to get more myself.
Huaizhu, Young Master Wangquan and the others have left?
They've all left.
Great! Peace and quiet at last.
I thought
they'd stick around and keep pestering you.
They have important matters to attend to.
Why? You seem to dislike him.
It's not that I dislike him.
I just prefer the masked guy.
Got that?
Where are you going to collect herbs today?
Miss Huaizhu,
we are going to Mount Cangyun today.
What's wrong?
Mount Cangyun is full of steep cliffs.
They're going to collect herbs
but didn't bring any climbing gear.
Now that you mention it,
it does seem a bit odd.
Qinlan,
while I was away,
did the rare herbs collected in the villa
actually increase?
Our income
has increased quite a bit because of it.
Strange.
Qinlan, go gather all the disciples.
I need to ask them something.
Okay.
This Wangquan Sword is newly forged.
Young Master, please take a look.
What a pity. A fake is still a fake.
It'll never become
the true greatest sword in the world.
Mr. Fei.
Do you remember the dream I had?
The so-called Eternal Night
is actually the Black Fox.
My father must have discovered something
beyond the Boundary,
but he can't return
and has to bide his time.
Young Master, do you mean
you want to go beyond the Boundary?
Don't worry, Mr. Fei.
The battle at Sky City
has shown me the power of the Black Fox.
I won't act recklessly.
I'll definitely find the Black Fox's weakness,
find my father,
and claim the true Wangquan Sword.
[Great Virtue Carries All Things]
Thousand-year-old ginseng,
Dendrobium officinale, and Clubmoss
are all worth a fortune.
These herbs grow on steep cliffs.
How did you gather them?
Naturally,
we climbed up there
and picked them ourselves.
Show me your hands.
It's inevitable to get scratched
gathering herbs on a mountain,
but your hands and feet
don't have any scratches,
and your clothes are intact.
Tell me,
how did you obtain these herbs?
That's right. Confess now.
Don't make me force it out of you.
Jin Renfeng.
You've enslaved demons to gather herbs.
That's strictly forbidden
by the Divine Fire Villa.
Do you admit your fault?
Master, it's the survival of the fittest.
I've merely enslaved a few demons
and made them gather herbs
to strengthen us.
What's wrong with that?
The Divine Fire Villa
has always treated humans and demons equally.
But now, all you see is strength and weakness,
not right and wrong.
Well then,
I'd like to challenge you
and see just how strong you really are.
All of you, step back.
[Great Virtue Carries All Things]
Alright, let's have a fire duel.
Master, please be our witness.
Junior Huaizhu,
you've mastered the Pure Yang Flame?